[{"answer": "A cute little place called La Bonisera in that place", "docId": "Invention-of-Lying_-The.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "I have very little money", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "I have very little money", "docId": "Invention-of-Lying_-The.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I don't know any of them", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Yes", "docId": "Invention-of-Lying_-The.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "I have a job at an office", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Well, it hasn't happened yet", "docId": "Invention-of-Lying_-The.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Okay, I'll be in my office", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Okay, but everybody knows you are", "docId": "Invention-of-Lying_-The.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Okay, I'll be searching for new jobs on my friend", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "What are you going to do now", "docId": "Invention-of-Lying_-The.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "I don't have much hope for you either, but I wish you good luck", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "I don't have much hope for you either, but I wish you good luck", "docId": "Invention-of-Lying_-The.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Bye, my friend", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": " Did you invent a new kind of bike", "docId": "Invention-of-Lying_-The.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Bone chicks asses. That's what I'd do", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Well, sort of", "docId": "Invention-of-Lying_-The.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "We couldn't lose", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Hold on, I think I found a flaw in your plan. How can they pay us if we have all the money in the world", "docId": "Invention-of-Lying_-The.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Well, they can't because we've got it all", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Wait, and I know you said you didn't want to date me ever again, but I'm different now. Things have changed. I think I'm in your league now", "docId": "Invention-of-Lying_-The.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "No. I'm not better looking. I'm just more... powerful. I think you have to see it for yourself", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "No. I'm not better looking. I'm just more... powerful. I think you have to see it for yourself", "docId": "Invention-of-Lying_-The.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "No, I haven't been to the gym. It's just... it's amazing. Things are different for me now. You have to see this. I think you'll hardly recognize me", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Just tell me what you told your grandmother", "docId": "Invention-of-Lying_-The.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "What you said obviously affected a lot of people. I don't think you have the choice to keep it in now", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Yes, of course. Everyone gets a mansion", "docId": "Invention-of-Lying_-The.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "If they want to live with you, they can leave their mansion and live in yours", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "I'm not sure. I just did it", "docId": "Invention-of-Lying_-The.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "I mean just that. You'll always be beautiful to me", "qsentId": 30}]